(Howard:)Sheldon still moping?
(Leonard:)Yeah, it's weird.
Even though he didn't want
(Leonard:)to give the lecture
in the first place,
(Leonard:)being rejected by those students
really hit him hard.
(Raj:)I know the feeling.
(Raj:)It's like accidentally
walking into a gay bar
(Raj:)and then having
no one hit on you.
(Raj:)It-It happened
to a friend of mine.
(Bernadette:)Are you guys doing okay?
(Howard:)Leonard and I are fine,
(Howard:)but I think Raj needs
to meet a girl really soon.
(Bernadette:)Well, that shouldn't
be too hard.
(Bernadette:)He's such a cutie.
(Raj:)Thank you,
but "cute" is for bunnies.
(Raj:)I want to be something
with sex appeal,
(Sheldon:)like...
like a labradoodle.
(Howard:)Labradoodle?
(Leonard:)We might be starting
to zero in on your problem.
(Bernadette:)Don't you listen to them.
(Bernadette:)You've got plenty
of sex appeal.
(Raj:)You really think so?
(Bernadette:)Yeah. You're a hottie.
(Raj:)Well, thanks, Bernadette.